australianshortfilms.com 2018-12-15

# Privacy Policy | Australian Short Films

This website is owned and operated by e-CBD Pty Ltd - an Australian web development company based on Queensland's Gold Coast.

### Our Privacy Policy

When you visit our web site, our web server automatically recognizes your Internet Protocol (IP) address. Your IP address is non-identifying and is used to compile statistics about traffic to our web site.

Personal information you provide us in 'feedback' forms and booking/reservation forms is collected for the sole purpose of processing your enquiry and contacting you to confirm details. Such personally identifying information is stored offline in a secure environment and should you want your personal details to be removed from our database you can do so at any time by e-mailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#234a4d454c63460e4041470d404c4e), or phoning us on +617 5531 3810.

We will only pass personal information onto third parties with whom you have made a booking, enquiry or reservation. Under no circumstance do we pass your information on to third parties which are not directly related to the processing of your booking, enquiry or reservation. We do not send out unsolicited email.

We may compile information regarding what pages visitors access or visit, but these statistics will not provide personally identifying details. By using our web site you are consenting to the collection and use of this information by this website.

If this website makes changes to its privacy policy, we will post such changes on this page so that you are always aware of what we collect.
